This one is much harder like you can
start with trace loop SDK report the
open telemetry tracing data to either
trace loop or any other vendor. This one
is easy but once it gets to defining and
configuring the or building the right
evals then it gets much harder and this
is the heavy lifting uh monitoring and
observing like LLM applications to
actually get valid insights back. What
would you say then as advice to people
who are trying to build eval suites?
What are the gotchas? What should people
look out for and where should they
start? You're listening to the AI native
dev brought to you by
[Applause]
[Music]
Tesla. Hello and welcome to another
episode of the AI native dev. My name is
Simon Maple and joining me today is Gal
Kleinman who is the CTO and co-founder
of Trace Loop. Welcome Gal. How are you?
Thank you. I'm great. How are you? I'm
doing very well, thank you. Yeah, not
too bad. It's just turning summer. Not
summer, but we're just turning into
spring in the UK. So, finally, we're
getting a little bit heat back in our
day. I'm all the better for a little bit
of sun. Cool. In the place I'm located
at, it's already summer. Like, it's 25°
outside. Stop.
You're hurting me. Yeah. So, Gal, tell
us a little bit about your story, your
journey before Trace Loop. First of all,
before Trace Loop, I will tell you
briefly about my last role before
starting Trace Loop. I was a group
manager at Fiverr leading a group
developing like the machine learning
platform for the data science teams at
Fiverr. Also another team who was
dealing with the data infrastructure.
This is it. Then once I left Fiverr
together with near my co-founder and the
CEO of Trace Loop we joined we we got
accepted to Y combinator batch winter 23
and like the rest is history from that
point trace loop fresh loop started.
Yeah. Awesome. And so trace loops in and
around the space of LLM observability
and we'll talk about that generally but
also a little bit about trace loop
itself as well. So I guess first of all
what's the problem I guess that trace
loop is trying to solve? What space is
it in? So we are at the space like the
famous space of LLM observability which
is a derivative of general observability
of applications. What we do actually and
what we solve in addition to the classic
classic observability is the part of
evaluation. the part of evaluation both
in real time like in terms of monitoring
your LLM application and helping you
improve your LLM application in the like
the development cycle
using mostly offline evaluations. So
that's that's the like the problem
definition or another problem but more
about the solutions we help you observe
and improve your LLM application using
using the findings from the production
and tracing. Yeah. Awesome. And what was
your inspiration or motivation almost to
to start trace loop? Was there a pain
point you had previously? Yeah, actually
during the Y combinator batch we've been
developing a totally different product.
It was like just the beginning of the
LLM and generative AI era. OpenAI has
just released SHA GPT and all of the GPT
models. We we've been developing a
solution which was based on a multi-
aent architecture. It was like rocket
science that days. Today every other
startup is developing autonomous agents.
But we've been developing autonomous
agents who which was which were supposed
to solve the generation of end to end
end to end tasks for distributed
systems. I know a lot of buzzwords but
this is what we've been dealing with
that time and we've got to to an MVP
somewhere at close to the end of Y
combinator batch. we've got to working
MVP of that architecture and it wasn't
it wasn't stable and it wasn't reliable
at all like always there is the argue
between me and near my co-founder
whether it was working 30 I claimed that
it was working 30% near as the CEO who's
supposed to be the optimistic between us
he claims that it was around between 60
to 70% working but It wasn't reliable at
all and we were afraid of going out of
out of beta with this product. At that
point we thought okay we got to have
some observability solution. We are a
startup. It's fine if it will be sprayb
at the first at the first day of our
product but we got to somehow observe
what happened what happens to our users
in production and using those
observations we got to we have to
improve our product continuously and get
to a point where it works I wouldn't say
perfectly because probably 100% is not
achievable with AI to a point where we
feel it's 90% working and it's a hard
work then we started developing
internally an observability solution
based on open telemetry which I guess we
will talk about later in this in this
podcast and the rest is history. Yeah,
it's really interesting as a startup to
understand when to go to when to go to
market at what time. And I think there's
a couple I guess there's a couple of
important things. One is meeting the
expectations of potential users or first
on boarding those first users. I guess
you there's probably an amount of that
which is in and around messaging in
terms of we don't want to promise too
much necessarily but we want to gau we
want to like level expectations but then
I guess the other important thing is we
call it at Tesla we call it developing
in a lab. You don't want to be
developing in a lab. You want to get
that external like real user feedback
and get that real user feedback in
early. Did you find I'm curious before
we jump into a little bit more around
the observability. Did you find that
once you pushed your product to market
and you started getting that user
feedback, was that an accelerator to
that percentage going from whether it
was 30 or 60 that that much higher or
was it a steady increase still similar
to how you were developing in the lab
before? I can tell you the the beautiful
story about yeah we launched the MVP and
then we improved our our accuracy from
30% to 90% in I don't know in a week or
two but I prefer to tell you the truth
that we were like we we fell in love
with the idea of observability for LLM
applications and then like that MVP was
never was never launched we since then
we've been working on on the LLM
observability solution
Yeah. Gotcha. Gotcha. Awesome.
Observability. Then let's talk a little
bit about for developers who are using
LLMs today, the need for LLM
observability. I guess what are the
biggest misconceptions that developers
have when they're trying to build an LLM
using an LLM? What are the biggest
misconceptions or falsehoods that I
guess that developers have about LLMs
whereby LLMs can really bite them if
they don't know about these?
I think like every everyone probably you
will talk to will say the same thing.
It's quite easy to get into a sort of
working P and most of the developers
they think because we think we are
better than others then we think that
okay no it's a super simple prompt and a
super simple pipeline and I know how it
will behave yeah we will develop that P
and quite quickly it will get into a
production grade application it is a
misconception the truth is that taking
application or The vast amount of the
vast amount of time is spent taking that
P which is working probably as I
mentioned in our idea which is working
probably 30% uh of the times taking this
one into a 90% working application this
is what you spend most of the time on
and this is this is a great
misconception also another misconception
is the fact that okay if I will just
have a way to see what happened what
happens in production or have have some
sort of simple tracing or simple logging
capabilities. this is what will help me
to get into like production grade
application that 90 90% dream also I
think it's a misconception and you need
to be much more sophisticated as this
solution does not scale and you can't go
for example trace by trace and monitor
that way your production traffic and by
that improve your application let's jump
into the some of the differences between
this black box of an LLM existing in our
app and just current our traditional
code even simple things like debugging
for example right it's easy for me to
step through my code and understand why
things happen and how things get to how
I get an answer out of that with an LLM
it's completely obviously different we
throw a prompt in we get a response and
it can be very this is my input this is
my output and actually if I give that
same input 10 times to the same LLM uh
with without context I will get 10
different answers how do we even think
about what are the fundamental
differences that we need to be aware of
when debugging or doing anything in
detail with a traditional application in
comparison to an LLM. So just as you
mentioned the fact that it's not
deterministic make it much more harder
to debug because even if I copy the
exact same example I saw in production
for example and try to mock it in my dev
environment I will probably not get the
same results which makes everything
harder to to debug test and fix in terms
of this is in terms of debugging but in
terms of observability
The big difference is the fact that in
classic observability we have the common
common metrics and way to to understand
which flow which flows didn't work as we
expected. For example, we can track
errors by I don't know looking for
status codes of HTTP for example like
looking for 500 status code or just
looking for exceptions. I don't know
looking for other metrics like latency
and stuff like that. These are all thing
that as engineers we are familiar with
and a lot of best practices were written
about about tracking those metrics and
by that understanding which flows are
misfunctioning in your application. when
we are getting to LLM based flows then
we have a whole a whole different space
of problems and the like the most tricky
stuff is understanding which actual
flows didn't work as we expected. Why it
is so hard? Because the whole term of
good or bad or su or between success and
failure, it's not that clear like it's
not a binary result. And even if we will
look at the same result, let's imagine
me and you look at the same response for
a prompt we gave to Chip. You can think
it's a good it's a good answer for the
question and I can think it's a bad
answer for the question. Even when you
look at like manual annotator manual
annotators and companies companies we
are working with then the practice is
usually taking more than one annotator
for each example because it is
subjective and there is no clear answer
for anything. Then you will have to set
up some metrics or way to evaluate what
what really happens in your in your
production and evaluate whether it's
good or bad. And this is a hard task
which we don't have in classic
observability.
Yeah. Yeah. It's so frustrating, right?
In order to
determine whether something is right or
wrong or it's not even like you say it's
not even right or wrong. There's a scale
of do you know what for most people this
will probably be right but actually
there's a group that this will be wrong.
That's so hard to ascertain. I guess the
second thing is in terms of in terms of
being able to test would you say that
it's harder to almost mock up production
like quality tests actual user flows or
compared to traditional input output or
do you think that's reasonable as well
because I guess you have to care about
not just here's a flow here's some input
and we get some expected output but it's
the intent of the user And is that user
satisfied with the result that they get?
So I guess my question is from a from
the point of view of actually even being
able to mock those tests from an
observability point of view, is it
harder as well in in development testing
scenarios to create those tests that are
representative of of production quality
flows and actually then work out if it's
correct or not in terms of responses.
Yeah, it's much harder in general to map
all the options, all the like all the
possible examples of input. As a result,
it's much harder to create a good
coverage or a good set of tests because
LLMs by their definition, they are quite
open-ended as long as you are not
scoping your application to super super
specific flows. For example, we can
think of some chatbot, some support
chatbot. So if I will just expose the LM
interface to the user and to my user and
tell him, okay, I'm a support chatbot.
Do ask me whatever you want, then the
amount of possibilities for the input is
endless. But if I will scope you and
this is a good practice in general for
for such products. If I will scope you
to stuff that AI chatbot can do then I
can scope the the variations of the
input and then it will be a little bit
easier to create good coverage for that
for those use cases. Yeah, I love that
structured inputs really reduce the the
level of variance that you could
receive. When we think about the
challenges that we face in the real
world today, we talked about some of the
problems that exist there from a
developer point of view, some of the
scenarios that that they might see as
potential issue. Hallucinations is the
obvious, I guess, when the LLM's just
make up that you just is false, but
obviously need some level of citation.
What are the other things that we as
developers or end users need to be
worried about? I guess that that we need
you know is a candidate that we can
identify in an observability point of
view. Just what we talked about earlier
like the terministic behavior which we
are used to does not exist in in this
world and this is an issue because we
can deploy some code to production which
involves some prompt or some pipeline or
LLM based some LLM based application and
what we saw for example with our one of
our customers is the performance or the
quality of the answers from that LLM can
degrade or drift a long time and this is
something to be aware of. Open AI for
example even like even if we're using
the exact same model with the revision
with the date of the release of that
model they are doing a lot of changes
not to the foundation model itself but
usually to the let's say to the
inference architecture like they have a
complex architecture which handles the
inference inference request and they are
having those those changes frequently
which can result in degradation in the
performance of your of your LLM calls.
Uh for example, we saw in our customers
that someday some random day they
realized that one of their summary tasks
or summary prompts it started they track
the amount of amount of words in the
summary as some proxy metric to the
quality of the to the quality of the
summary. And some random day they
realized that the median that the median
number of words in the summary just
decreased dramatically. I guess it was
around 20 20 words which is quite
significant in in their case because the
whole summary was about between 50
to 150 words as far as I remember. Don't
catch me here. But a lot of changes can
happen during even if you tested your
code and everything is working someday
everything can change and affect
dramatically your your product.
Obviously there is the case of
hallucinations which I guess it is so
widely discussed but I don't know if I
can add a lot more in these terms. Yeah.
No, that makes sense. That makes sense.
So let's jump into some of the
observability terms. them. We mentioned
open telemetry at the start and open
almetry which I think is maybe was that
coined by Patrick Devoir. Yeah, exactly.
It was he he loves naming things doesn't
he? Tell us a so first of all why don't
you just remind us what open telemetry
is? Open telemetry it's a CNCF project
totally open source which is like
formalizing standardizing structuring
the way applications applications in our
area of distributed systems and complex
systems and architectures of SAS should
report metrics logs and tracing data
that way and they provide a lot of SDKs
and tools around it like collectors
which we can discuss it later if you
want. I'm not sure how important is it
in in this phase, but they provide a lot
of tools reporting data and
instrumenting client client libraries
mostly. And when I'm talking about
client libraries, I'm talking about SDKs
and and stuff like that mostly for a
back end. Today it's also exist in the
client and even in mobile I think so.
And you can report structured tracing
data to any destination since it's
standardized. So every destination and
every observability platform which
supports open telemetry and exposes open
telemetry endpoint can consume and
visualize and present in in their
application. I hope it makes sense. I'm
not sure it was clear at all but that's
good. It's good. Open Lmetry now that
sits on top of open telemetry. tell us a
little bit about what that does and I
guess the differences once we so as I
mentioned every open telemetry they have
their contrib and also I think in the
main repo they provide a lot of a lot of
instrumentations and instrumentation is
actually a library or a sub library in
let's take the example of python it's a
package who's wrapping a specific
specific SDK for example we can think of
I don't know if you have in Python you
are working with posgress and you use
SQL alchemy as as your client or OM so
open telemetry instrument they have open
telemetry instrumentation for SQL
alchemy which is wrapping the library
and knows how to extract the data in
some magic way out of the SDK methods
and report it in a standard way as open
telemetry logs traces metrics. What we
did with open lomemetry back then we
were looking for an observ how to report
let's call it observability data which
is actually traces we saw it as traces
because we thought oh there are we've
been developing agents it reminded us
some microservices architecture with you
have an orchestrator and which is the
agent or a lot of agents communicating
with each other. You have the
orchestrator then you have sort of
micros service which is agent which is
doing something as a tool for another
agent. So I thought oh open telemetry
can make can make a lot of sense in in
these terms in these terms as well maybe
that's a good like we are both me and
near my co-founder we have we are quite
experienced engineers and as long as you
become as long as you become an
experienced engineer you realize that
you don't have to invent the wheel for
every task you are doing and as much you
are adapting as much you are adopting
already developed solutions or out
ofthebox solutions then I guess you
become a better better engineer at least
in my opinion so we thought okay open
telemetry could be or can be a great
tool for the purpose of observing agents
observing LLM applications because even
if you are not developing agents the
pipelines uh were getting more and more
complex that time and involved also API
calls and stuff like that which is super
innative to open telemetry because HTTP
calls are being instrumented over there.
So we thought okay let's adopt open
telemetry. Back then once we realized it
we said okay let's create a repository a
project which is extending open
telemetry. What we've just added is a
set of instrumentation or most of the
relevant SDKs and libraries during the
development of LLM based applications.
It is combined of three different types
of
instrumentations. One is for foundation
models. You can find their open AI,
anthropic, bedrock, gemini and or vertex
AI and and so on. We have 40 40
instrumentations today or something
around that. I can't I don't even count
it anymore anymore. We have their vector
databases instrumentations and
frameworks. The third pillar is
frameworks like lench chain, lama index,
crewi, hay stack and and other friends.
That way we provide instrumentations for
most of the building blocks of of LLM
applications.
Combining this one with the already
existing the already existing
instrumentations provided by open
telemetry and using the mechanism of
open telemetry, we are able to to report
or ingest open telemetry data both to
our platform but also to any other
observability platform supporting open
telemetry. And you can see like a great
you can observe and see great traces
which contains the prompts the responses
some metadata around that like the token
tokens used the cost for every call the
let's say the top K documents you've
retrieved from from your vector database
the transformation the transform tasks
inside the frameworks like langchain and
llama index and a lot more data you can
get get it for free. You just have to
initialize our SDK like trace loop and
you get it out of the box. So what would
the best practices be someone starting
with LM observability? Is there an
amount that would need to be set up in
terms of obviously does everything get
switched on and then you apply alerts
apply kind of like thresholds which you
care about. How much configuration does
there need to be per application based
on subtle differences between
implementations? So if you are just
working with the basic tracing and the
basic metrics that that are provided
from the SDK it's only the raw data then
you will have the classic the classic
observability metrics let's say the
deterministic ones the token usage and
latency and stuff like that you can set
and configure alerts and monitors based
on that. So as a first step, it's a good
step towards the direction of of being
monitored and being covered, but it's
not enough to be honest. As we talked as
we talked before, what's more important
is defining defining evaluations in
production which are using the which are
using the the real content of the
response and trying to evaluate and
score the response itself and not the
metadata metrics. Yeah. And is that the
is that one of the kind of hardest
things if you think about the lift that
it need that a user needs in terms of
getting good observability data back is
creating the right
eval is that the lift from the user
point of view. Yeah, this one is much
harder like you can start with trace
loop SDK report the open telemetry
tracing data to either trace loop or any
other vendor. This one is easy but once
it gets to defining and configuring the
or building the right evals then it gets
much harder and this is the heavy
lifting monitoring and observing like
LLM applications to actually get valid
insights back. What would you say then
as advice to people who are trying to
build eval suites? What are the gotchas?
What should people look out for and
where should they start?
So from what we
s I will say like a good starting point
can be working with some proxy metrics
which usually can be they can be
slightly naive like I mentioned the word
count and stuff like that. It can be a
good proxy for some cases,
but if you want to take it one step
further than what we saw at least, it is
super dependent on the context of your
application. There is no silver bullet
and general metrics which you know which
tend to be used in classic NLP, I don't
know, rouge, grun, they are all great
matrix. they just didn't provide the
usually the expected the expected result
and you you will have to uh find your
evals and provide the context of your
evalu of your application. It requires a
lot of like you first have to manual
annotate data and and understand as a
person as a human annotating or
evaluating the responses I got to first
understand which criterias I want to
evaluate myself and make sure that as a
human I can evaluate it and get
consistent result results with other
humans for example. Yeah. And I think
that's really interesting actually
because I think it's one of those hard
ones where you actually don't really
know how good your eval is because it
could provide you with some results. Say
certain models are better than others.
Say certain changes are better than
others. You don't really know until it's
in production, right? Because it's only
when you get users that are happier or
less happy based on the results that
that you actually know whether your LLMs
are providing good value. Is that fair
in all cases or I think maybe with the
structured inputs structured outputs
there's probably a little bit more more
of a measurability without having to
rely on users sentiment but yeah does it
feel like sometimes we're guessing a
little bit with
eval we need to truly get that
production level user feedback so to be
honest as far as I see it user feedback
when you ask for it explicitly it tends
to be biased like it's not a it's not a
good metric. If you want to take
something from production, then I will
look for for implicit scoring by users.
Let's say I'm working on a product who
suggesting completions, then if the user
actually accepted my completion, I can
count it as a thumb up. But if I will
proactively ask for his feedback,
usually it tends it tends to be biased
because probably you will get only the
angry most of the time you will get the
angry users and even if you have 90% of
them which are actually satisfied you
will see only the ones who who are
angry. setting up valuations. We believe
by the way in using real production data
and examples. It can be it can be hard
in terms of in terms of privacy of data
for some for some companies who you know
everyone respects their the privacy of
their clients and their customers. So
not everyone can do it but if you can do
it and take examples from real world
like real world use cases within your
product then you can use this one to
train evaluators which you can then use
during your development process. Yeah.
Yeah. Makes sense. From a trace data
point of view and an alerts point of
view is there are there ever problems in
and around kind of like signal to noise
ratio between the traces? Is there is is
it hard to create alerts that are
meaningful?
Yeah, definitely because you can at the
beginning you can go trace by trace and
it's fine. You do it manually. Most of
the companies are doing it even the
biggest ones because they start with a
really small really small roll out of
the LLM feature they are launching. So
it's fine you can go trace by trace.
Then you use as I mentioned like the
basic metrics of latency and stuff like
that and you think it solve it solves
your issue but once you get you get to
like a significant scale you can't go
trace by trace. So if you don't have the
capability or the right evaluators set
up and developed before then you find
yourself with let's say I don't know a
million a million generations a day and
it just it just doesn't doesn't scale
even if you want to spend a lot of a lot
of money on the problem and put a lot of
human resources it feels like super
super primitive going over a million of
examples every day and tag them. So you
gota set up the right evaluations and
the right evaluators to score the traces
in production and that way get only the
interesting one the interesting traces
and investigate and debug them in order
to improve your application. Yeah. And
in terms of who users typically are for
this kind of thing, how how much is the
spread of these types of activities done
by developers say versus versus folks
who are more on the operation side? The
whole world of the whole space of AI and
NML development has shifted towards
towards back-end developers and even
front-end developers today are
developing those features and
applications. When it was data
scientists developing these
applications, they are used to work with
they have they got to have some
evaluation some evaluation system and
like the practice and they working more
in a more methodical way because they
trained they were trained to do but
today backend engineers they are not
used to do it. So a lot of the effort is
going towards the is shifting to the
operations side. You can find a lot of
teams which existed even before like in
classic data science teams for example
they tend to use it in the past
annotation teams or which are creating
and curating data sets of label data.
Hey, product managers can do it,
annotation teams or domain experts,
which makes sense actually because if
I'm building, for example, let's imagine
a doctor, a medical doctor who's based
on on AI, on generative AI, then it
makes much more sense that a doctor will
rank and score and label the responses
of the LLM instead of the back-end
developer who understanding like I have
some understanding ing in like in health
just
because my just because I was trained I
was trained for the by by my family but
the common developer usually does not
understand anything in health so it's
better if a doctor will be the one to
the responses
yeah yeah cool let's look a little bit
forward now and think about what's
happening in the future obviously
agentic AI is something that's
absolutely flying right now and everyone
wanting to be more and more agentic.
There's talk of everyone being close to
AGI, but let's assume that's a few years
off. I think that's a fair assumption.
With those types of things where LM are
users of LM as well and you have
orchestrators of of agents, does that
make does this make things harder for
from an observability point of view as
data and things are being passed between
agents and between various flavors of
LMS, various vendors of LMS within the
same application? Does it make it
harder? and what's the importance of
observability in that space? Yeah,
definitely as as much as the like the
flows and the use cases of LLM
applications will get more and more
complex then observability will play a
much major role in in that game. And
why? Because today imagine a flow which
is only based on a single single prompt
to the same model every time. If one of
my users like he has an issue, it is
super simple or quite simple to
understand. Why? Because the flow is
super simple. But once it get it gets
much more complex and there are a lot of
there are more prompts more prompts
involved more models involved more
databases more tools like you can today
access the whole world of MCPS we didn't
cover it it at all but you can access
Google you can do a lot of stuff and you
got to somehow understand and trace what
happened along that way in order to
understand and debug
Both if you have an existing ticket from
a customer and you want to debug it, but
also and this is more of the space we
are dealing with understanding the
health and the quality and of the
generation of your system. So you want
to break it down like if I get some
general score for example of I don't
know it's 50% working but I don't know
how to break it down and when it get
when the flow get gets complex it's much
harder to break it down or you have a
lot more components that you want to
build some dashboard and understand
which is the leaking component which
makes me be only 50% at the end. It is
possible that all the rest like I have
all of the components functioning at I
don't know 90% 90% quality let's say and
one which is which is leaking and having
like missed malfunctioning and having a
bad performance. I want to be able to
track this one and understand which
exact component is in charge of this
one. Yeah. Yeah. No, that makes complete
sense. Otherwise, the black box just
gets bigger and you have no idea then
which part is at fault. That makes a lot
of sense. Let's wrap up Gal and I guess
from a developer point of view is there
a takeaway around managing observability
across apps that are using LLM that you
would kind of say this is the thing that
a developer needs to know about or needs
to do. This is the most important thing
that they should know. What would that
be? quite a cliche but there is that
thing what is not what is not measured
cannot be improved and what is not
improved is always degraded. It makes a
lot of sense in in this space and
actually this is the problem we are
dealing with. How do you measure the
actual the actual quality of your
responses and once you are able to
measure it you can improve it and you
can make sure it isn't it isn't
degraded. This is what I would expect
every developer to have in mind and this
is I think the main or the key takeaway
I'm going out with from this space.
Yeah. Yeah. Which is quite a classic
observability takeaway as well. So it's
almost don't discount your LLM from an
observability point of view. It needs to
be it needs to be held as accountable as
every other part of your app from a from
an observability point of view. And you
need to you absolutely need to know
what's happening. Don't just leave this
piece of magic that exists in your
application without without measuring it
which which is excellent advice. Gal,
thank you very much. This has been super
relevant to our audience. I think it's I
think it's super important that we when
we do introduce these things and I
remember years ago I've said this to a
few folks on the podcast years ago. We
used to scrutinize these LLMs that we
add into our apps much much more than we
do today. It's amazing how mainstream
LMS in applications or in our workflows
has become and how prevalent it is and
how accepted it is. But I think we need
to apply the same rigorous measures and
practices that we do across LMS as we do
our traditional code. So yeah, love this
session on observability and some really
nice practical insights there. So gal
very much appreciate your time. Thank
you for your insights. Thank you. I had
a great time.
Awesome. And thanks all for listening.
Make sure you if you enjoyed the
session, make sure you subscribe. Give
us a thumbs up on YouTube as well. And
thanks for tuning in and we'll see you
next time. Bye for
[Music]
now. Thanks for tuning in. Join us next
time on the AI Native Dev brought to you
by Tesla.
[Music]